[说话人1] First of all, thank you EDG for being here with us. We are going to start with some questions on the call. And can you go first?
[说话人1] 我想问一下奥特牧教练今天图一防守底细被破得很明显问题出在哪然后你觉得对估失败最关键的原因是什么呢
[说话人1] This question is for Autumn that for today's map 1, I think for your defend this really lost a lot. So what do you think is the issue for today's matchup especially for your defend today?
[说话人1] Yeah, our depends plan was not worked. So maybe the preparation for depends system was wrong. That's why we lost.
[说话人1] 我觉得今天我们所有做的关于扫手的一些计划可能没有走下所以说可能我们的一些准备工作一些准备体系做的没有那么好这是我们今天是来的主要原因
[说话人2] Thank you so much, now we are off. And then do you have another question?
[说话人2] 等等等等深夜快乐就有看
[说话人2] Happy birthday, Kung-Kaw! Thank you!
[说话人2] Thank you so much.
[说话人2] Now we are going to take some questions here in the room.
[说话人1] 哈囉,這裡是化龍電競我的問題是給到康康選手那麼很遺憾這次圣地亞哥的旅程是結束了但是你的22色彩剛剛開始那想問一下,今天有沒有什麼生日願望可以跟我們大家一起分享一下
[说话人1] I'm sorry for the loss today but your 22nds just begin so what's your birthday wish for your birthday? Do you share with us?
[说话人2] 또 부숴면. 여러분들 볼 Dana아 지금
[说话人2] I'm so sorry I don't know how to say it.
[说话人2] another question
[说话人1] 好 沒關係 那最後想說少年星期是不可再生之五還是希望你們能夠總結這一次的經驗然後繼續項目 想繼續奮鬥 繼續戰鬥 謝謝
[说话人1] And I think all your pride is really precious, it's really important for us. And I hope you who fix all the things and gain enough experience this time and keep fighting to your dream.
[说话人2] You're waiting, they will, the one-coats are happening. So we were thinking one minute.
[说话人1] Can I go from?
[说话人2] Estamos esperando que acaben los workouts y seguimos con el conferencio.
[说话人2] 因为现在选手在出场所以说我们可能稍微延迟一下大家稍等一分钟 满上开始
[说话人1] your fans are going to start this.
[说话人2] Okay, we will continue with this press conference now the sound is low-work.
[说话人1] We have another question here in the room.
[说话人1] Thank you. My question goes for teacher.
[说话人2] Chichu, your one of the strongest teams from China was the biggest difference that you feel when playing against international teams compared to China.
[说话人2] 这个问题是问到求求选手的因为其实你们也是连最强的队伍之一那你觉得在和国际队伍比赛的时候我先的队伍相比最大的不同是
[说话人2] 我觉得最大的一台在于不同是外的对付很能抓住我们的食物然后去得分吧这一件是个
[说话人1] 很大的一个需要我们需要感兴跟学习的一个人民
[说话人2] I think the biggest difference is the team from international leagues. It's like they don't know how to punish us to find our mistakes at the good timing and to grab the points.
[说话人1] Thank you so much and I'll see you soon.
[说话人2] Hello, my name is Raul Litz. I work for Fusion Esports. My question is for Smoggi. Smoggi, what do you think is going on with BCD China? Results haven't been grid-ladied. What do you think is behind that?
[说话人2] 这个问题是问到Smoggy选手的因为可能最近间的成绩并没有那么的领象觉得主要的原因是什么的
[说话人1] 我覺得跟全球就是差不多吧
[说话人2] 我觉得上了这种比赛以后失务会比较多然后过来的会抓住我们这些失务去得分
[说话人2] I think my answer is pretty similar as Choshu just said before. When we come to international stage, I think all the teams from other regions, they're good at finding time to punish us to punish our mistakes.
[说话人1] dentalabilities mar oğlum
[说话人1] Hello, my name is Zell from Command Kick.
[说话人1] Is glitching in for nobody?
[说话人2] Nobody, please, you are living in the team and in the comeback in the second round. What is your work? What do you think that the other team did best that you?
[说话人2] 這個問題是溫到Nobody選手的因為其實今天在第二輪的時候你帶領隊伍也實在了一個小小的力轉雖然說最後沒得一下比賽的勝利那你覺得今天對方隊伍做的比較好的部分是什麼
[说话人1] 脫夜跟团对面就是
[说话人2] 也是改变了很多,然后很好地可能跟他们今天比赛有的时候是不一样的然后感觉对面也是很好地发挥的他们的账容特性
[说话人2] I think for both of them, today they've changed a lot and it's really different of the place they'll compare with them before. I think also today they're really...
[说话人1] They have a conf design for today's match-up and they show all the stress they have.
[说话人1] Thank you so much, now we are going to take some questions on the call pervamedo to go.
[说话人2] Yes, Pedro Merrill, independent journalist, likewise, commissarations on this series and the subsequent elimination from his competition. Hope we can see a much stronger EDG in the future. I want to send this question over to Hong Kong. Obviously, you're no stranger to having to absorb eliminations in the international level. Of course, this is another chapter in this story of yours. But still, you've been able to overcome these past issues and get to championship glory in the past. What I want to ask you, though, is as you begin to reflect as to the issues of only wrong for this team in this competition.
[说话人1] Is this emotions, feelings, frustrations similar to what it was back then or is it different in this case? It put in particular for this year from your opinion?
[说话人1] 其实低纪在外界有限一定隐养上报道包卓行后你才全宣承儿头讨厌它但是我觉得这е给是黑金泡也有一个阿非常好的褻那我们现在在这多ため的粹子对你们所作的所有过程的讧 voyce和白这输胜去吧这输胜是等于这么说我设 veteransえて能经历
[说话人2] 其实对我来的前面是一个农区在看所以说没有错过的有没有感
[说话人2] 其实我变了一个我们换上照来然后换了一位联系星的选手然后我们现在就我打的时候我感觉就是一个星的阵容然后对我来说是一个星的开始
[说话人2] 我觉得我们一定会越来越好的因为后面还有很多比赛要打我觉得现在这种错败感对我来说其实没有什么感觉我只希望我们后面今年
[说话人1] 下半年或者年中能够打得更好然后把我们输了都赢回来
[说话人2] I think this year is like a brand new start for me. I don't feel that frustrated as before, because we have a new coach, we have a new player, and it's totally new roster of ever gaming. And I also believe that in the future, we'll become better.
[说话人1] because we still have a lot of matchups to play and I hope in the future we could win all the things and get back.
[说话人2] Thank you so much. Make a new route the next question.
[说话人1] Hi, I'm Miketorrez from Kitchen News. This question is for Autumn. From my coaching perspective, what would you say is the biggest challenge when playing on an international stage?
[说话人2] I already have many experience in international stages.
[说话人2] I just want to focus on the improvement.
[说话人2] from our experience like this.
[说话人1] We already know what was our problem on our fine depends and problem like haven't attacked. We already know that and I think this
[说话人1] even you lose, but I think that can be some our occulturement.
[说话人1] from this list. So we just I want to think this international stage is just as our experience.
[说话人2] for our better future.
[说话人2] Thank you so much. Now we have another question from Per Romero in the hole.
[说话人1] This was going to be also for autumn just out of curiosity. This was the match between your team and T1 Obviously your past team. I want to know just out of curiosity. Have you had any time to like Give some next-style mutations or any greeting sand You know after this result. I want to know if like you have any words for like T1 Just just like maybe give them good luck for the rest of the competition or anything else of that nature
[说话人2] 吼밤라
[说话人2] I am the one who know their hard working and
[说话人2] their passion for achieving something in every moment.
[说话人1] Tolong mempunyai
[说话人2] 저항이라 며칠inated, 생각 ??? 추 song 이制 weiß 쎄
[说话人2] Thank you so much. Now we are going to take the last question, killing the wrong one.
[说话人2] Hello guys, this is Matias from Magtrez. My question is for nobody.
[说话人1] How did you feel with the Santiago crowd? Did it motivate you in your matches or was it sometimes like distracting to you? How did you feel in your staying in Santiago?
[说话人1] 這個問題是問到《Noronoghoudi選手》的你對剩下歌整體的關注和關注分為有什麼樣的感覺在比賽中你覺得它會比較激勵你還是有些手可能會讓你有一些分析呢
[说话人1] 我觉得这边的观众就首先非常热情嘛然后其实在比赛里面就大家都会发现的给自己喜欢对我打扣嘛
[说话人1] 然后其实我觉得挺好的,包括这个舞台,你观众也挺近的,我觉得
[说话人2] I think the audience here is really passionate and the audience they are rooting for the team they like and also our stage is really close to all the crowd so the web is here is amazing.
[说话人1] Thank you so much, now we have one question from Mario.
[说话人2] And this is the last one.
[说话人1] Hi, how you doing? Can you talk a little bit more about your uniform? I think that is pretty special that has some talent, she and had a lot of things about masters. Can you talk a little bit about more about that?
[说话人1] 其實想問一下各位關於你們的對付因為我們覺得設計的很特別融合了很多當地的文化以及一些大時代的元素可以跟我們聊一下
[说话人2] 任何人回答都可以
[说话人1] 这个对付就是
[说话人2] 就是我们EZG的管理层他们操作的嘛就是他们去设计给我们的我们每次的大学校对我都不一样嘛然后这个上面是有这个致力地图在上面然后
[说话人1] 用了白色也是因为之前可能比赛的时候
[说话人1] 白色对付的对我都比较幸运嘛所以这算没有技能下来
[说话人2] The design is made by our management. Every time we come to global events, we all have different kind of uniforms. And this time, we have the night of San Diego on our clothes. And sometimes, we think white means lucky in the past.
[说话人1] So we need that lucky this time, but unfortunately we didn't manage the gateway.
[说话人1] Thank you so much. With this question we conclude this press conference. Thank you all for being here. Now without a surprise from the fans.
[说话人2] Chicos, como algunos ya habrán escuchado, hoy es el cumpleaños de Cancan. Así que nos gustaría cantarle cumpleaños feliz, como lo hacemos aquí en Chile. We're going to sing Happy Birthday to Cancan, as we do here in Chile. So, uno, dos, tres. Cumpleaños feliz.
[说话人1] Te deseamos a...
[说话人1] Happy birthday. Yes. Well, thank you guys.
[说话人1] Thank you very much and thank you DG for being here with us in Master Santiago.
[说话人1] We hope to see you in another tournament. Thank you.